It's so naughty.
すごいエッチだね
Shelta-kun?
シェルタくん?
It's so naughty.
すごいエッチだね
Shall I wave my hand back?
後ろへ手を振りましょうか
Do you want to turn your back?
後ろに向けますか
So, I'm going to sit here like this, like this.
じゃあ、ここでこうやって、こんな感じで座ります
Put your feet down.
足は下に下ろして
Look this way.
こっち向いて
So, can you sit with short legs?
じゃあ、短い脚で座れる?
Can I ask you some questions in this situation?
この状態でいろいろ聞いていってもいいですか?
So, may I ask you to introduce yourself again?
じゃあ、改めてご紹介してもらっていいですか?
Your name.
お名前を
This is Miyanna.
ミヤンナです
How old are you?
おいくつですか?
I'm 20 years old.
20歳です
Was it at a movie theater?
映画館でしたっけ?
What was your favorite hobby?
好きな趣味って何でしたっけ?
Movie theater.
映画館所
Was it indoors?
インドアなんでしたっけ?
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
Something sweet.
甘いもの
Do you watch YouTube?
YouTubeとか見るんですか?
I'll see.
見ます
I think there's YouTube, Instagram, and TikTok.
YouTube、インスタ、TikTokってあると思うんです
But which one are you?
けど、 どれ派ですか?
TikTok?
Can you dance?
踊れるの?
Just look.
見るだけ
That's right.
そう なんだ
TikTok is interesting.
TikTok面白いね
Do you have a favorite idol?
好きなアイドルとかいるんですか?
Are you not really interested in men's Johnny's?
男性のジャニーズとかあんまり興味ない?
Girl idols.
女の子のアイドルとか
Oh, really?
あ、 そう?
I like it.
好きです
And is it Korean K-POP?
しかも韓国系K-POPなんだっけ?
Isn't that said in K-POP?
K-POPで言うてないですか?
Are you a group?
グループですか?
Idols, Espa, etc.
アイドルとか、エスパとか
Are you the type of person who is said to be beautiful?
綺麗って言われたりタイプですか?
Are you the type of person who calls you cute?
かわいいって言われたりタイプですか?
I might be happier if it's cute.
かわいいのほうが嬉しいかも
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
It's cute.
かわいいなんだ
Is there a type of man you like?
好きな男性のタイプとかあります?
A person of high sex.
性高い人
A sexual person?
性高い人?
In terms of appearance.
見た目だと
180 or more?
180以上?
Oh, more?
あ、もっと?
No, that's about it.
いや、それぐらい
What's inside?
中身はどうですか?
A very kind person.
めっちゃ優しい人
Are you a very kind person?
めっちゃ優しい人?
A very kind person.
めっちゃ優しい人
No angry people?
怒る人ダメ?
A very kind person.
めっちゃ優しい人
Ah, I guess so.
あ、そうだろう
So, what kind of personality do you think you are?
だから、自分はどういう性格だと思いますか?
I might be quite shy at first.
自分は結構人見知りかも、最初は
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Not at all once we become friends.
仲良くなったら全然
So now I'm in a very shy state.
じゃあ今はすごい人見知りの状態なんですね
is that so.
そうですか
Do you have a desire to get married?
結婚願望ありますか?
there is.
あります
Do you have it?
ありますか
How long do you think it will take?
いつぐらいとかって考えてます?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Not right now, right?
今すぐじゃないよね?
Do you think you want children?
子供とか欲しいと思います?
If I could.
できたら
What message do you have for yourself 10 years from now?
10年後の自分に何かメッセージってあります?
I'm 30 years old.
30歳ですよ
difficult.
難しい
I want it to be like this.
こうなってて欲しいとか
It's important.
大 事だね
This is a very serious story, but
めっちゃ真面目な話なんですけど、
What do you think about the current somewhat dark situation?
今のなんか、 暗いな情勢についてどう思いますか?
I don't know.
わかんない
That's right.
そうだよね
What do you think about Trump?
トランプさんってどう思います?
What do you think about the face?
顔は思う?
I understand Mr. Trump, but still.
トランプさんは分かるけど、今も
Ah, yes.
ああ、そう
Even my uncle doesn't know anything about it.
おじさんも全然知らないから
Did you cum inside?
中に出したし?
Does your lower back tense up?
腰が力を入れる?
Just sit up on your back.
ちょっと背中を起きて
Can I make my hands normal?
手を普通にしていい?
by
バイ
by.
Did you see it?
見 ました?
I let out a lot.
い っぱい出しちゃった
Shall we put it in?
入れてみようか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
You can put it out a little.
少し出しにできる
Try putting it out
出しにしてみ
Okay?
よう か
You can put it out a little.
少し出しにできる
Just a little bit more.
もう ちょっと、 出しきり
that,
それ、
Shall we put it out there?
出 しにしてみようか